<!-- 
TODO:


-->

14.02:
Fixed bulk tea recipe

14.01:
Perodyne can be stored in stockpiles

14.00:
Added tiered upgradable book storage - Book Rack, Bookshelf, Bookcase
Thurible no longer works outside
Thurible shows its area of effect
Added Arcade construction table
Empty arcades can be built
Arcade cartridges can be copied and installed into empty arcades
Painting and dartboard automatically minify themselves when their wall is missing
Removed go table and reversi table
Fixed book reading reportString


<!-- Alpha 13 and lesser versions -->

v3.21:
Tightened dartboard accuracy
Dartboard has "teams" (each player uses a different colored dart)
Dartboard shows standing area when selected

v3.20:
Requires corePanda v13.2
Fixed cross-mod naming conflicts

v3.10:
Added CorePanda as a dependency, moved some assets (check corePanda changelog)
Fixed dart rotation
Thurible description better describes its function
Reading tables no longer require books to build
Colonists now grab a book from a nearby bookcase, then read it at a reading table
Book name list can be added to in: Defs/BookNameDefs/BookNames_AJO.xml

v3.02:
Colonists now actually use the dartboard

v3.01:
Replaced missing base reference

v3.00:
Added dartboard
Fixed easel icon rotation
Added thurible - provides joy to all in room as long as it's fueled
Added AEA tank - fuel for the thurible, comes in multiple scents

v2.81:
Fixed painting placement - must be placed on a constructed wall

v2.80:
updated to a13
Redrew graphics
Reworked Perodyne - now gives 2x joy, stages balanced
Drinking spectago tea reduces colonists social fight factor

v2.75:
Increased paper recipe yield from 20 to 100
Increased paper stack limit from 50 to 500
Added a reading table that can be constructed using written books
Fixed painting icon in trader menu

v2.74:
Redrew paintings, now appear to hang on the wall

v2.73:
Fixed written book art descriptions	

v2.72:
Blank books can be bought from joy traders
Bookcase registered as HighQuality - quality traits and art
Bookcase base price lowered from 500 to 400 (also affected by quality)
Refactored writing system
  Bookcases now boost WritingSpeed by 10% each, to a maximum of +20%
  Writing speed is impacted by how impressive the room is
  Increased writing time for books
  Rebalanced WritingSpeed stats
Paintings no longer show as sculptures on the Art tab
Written books now have a title and an art description
Written books max stack size reduced to 1
Written books moved to Art category

v2.71:
Culled changelog - full log available int the /About/Changelog.xml
Reduced Perodyne stack to 10 to limit cargo pod imbalance (500+ pills being delivered)

v2.70:
Raised spectago minimum light level from 30% to 60%
Spectago can be grown in plant pots for decoration
Code cleanup
Changed resources category to manufactured
Added WritingSpeed stat
Added Paper, Blank Book, Unfinished Book, Written Book, Writing Table
Added recipes for book binding and writing 

v2.60:
Spectago can now be found in the wild
Increased Perodyne stack size to 100
Added CCL v0.12.3b as a dependency
  Arcades now only consume power when in use, and give off a small amount of light
  Paintings now must be placed onto a wall
  Now must be placed under a roof: arcades, card table, RimColony, bookcase

v2.52:
Added bulk recipe for spectago tea using the brewery
Perodyne sold by medical transporters if Rim Pharma is installed
Perodyne includes side effects list in description. Side effects based on normal dosage.

v2.51:
Removed nutrition value on Perodyne
Perodyne no longer has a 100% knockout rate when "wasted" overdosed
Lowered cost of Perodyne in response to Methophine (Rim Pharma drug)

v2.50:
Removed random paintings, allow painting rotation using single graphic until fix can be found
Balanced prices and beauty of items
Removed Thrumbo Energy (moved to Soda Brewing mod)
PREVIOUS SAVES: If you have Thrumbo Energy present on the map, you must either drink/sell them all, or download the Soda Brewing mod
Teetotalers can now drink Spectago Tea
Removed deterioration rate

v2.40:
Added research project for more efficient paint making
Added recipe for tempera paint (yields more, unlocked with research)
Added Perodyne, a euphoric painkiller
Added Thrumbo energy drink

v2.31:
Aligned arcades closer to walls (visual)
Remade rotated Bookshelf graphics 
Bookshelves now offer a joy job
Fixed issue with Reading Table being unusable with chairs

v2.30:
Added Glutendogs (Animal skill arcade)
Added rotation graphics to all arcade cabinets
Reduced prices of arcades from 1,200 to 1,000 (prices still vary based on quality)
Textures folder now includes source .XCFs for modders / curious people

v2.21:
Tested with A12d - working
Arcades no longer appear on the Furniture tab in the Architect.

v2.20:
Updated to A12, should work with A12b/c/d

v2.13:
Fixed errant line of code causing the Elder Scones arcade to appear distorted.

v2.12:
Paintings can now be stored properly in stockpiles. Found under the Art tab

v2.11:
Fixed A11b conflict involving unfinished things, should be fully compatible with A11b now

v2.10:
Added unfinished painting
Balanced painting time
Added credits list for paintings used
Painting supplies now stack to 10
Easel only costs wood to build; paintings cost 1 painting supplies + 1 cloth
Added spectago flower for paint making
Added tea made from the spectago petals

v2.02:
Fixed issue with Bookcase being unplaceable.

v2.01:
Fixed RimColony reportString to correctly show current activity.

v2.00:
Added Bookcase, Reading Table, Easel, Painting, Painting Supplies, Pile of Books, and Pleasure Cruiser(trader).
Arcades no longer require stool, can now be rotated.
Added optional patch removing skill gain

v1.20:
Updated to Alpha 11, finishing v2 features.

v1.10:
Added reversi table, card table, RimColony, and 7 arcades

v1.00:
Initial release for Alpha 10. Includes go table and 4 arcades